const contest_1_2 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Factorize completely $a^{4}+4 a^{3} b+6 a^{2} b^{2}+4 a b^{3}+b^{4}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "a plus b all to the power 4",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Algebra", "Polynomial Factorization"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "In how many ways can 5 persons be seated in a row of 5 seats.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "120",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Combinatorics", "Permutations"]
    },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 3,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Find the coordinates of the point of inflexion of the curve $y=x^{3}-6 x^{2}+$ $16 x$.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "2 and 16",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Mathematics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Calculus", "Curve Analysis"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 4,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "In genetics, how many sets of sister chromatids make a tetrad?",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "Two sets of sister chromatids",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Biology",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Genetics", "Cell Division"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 5,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "What name is given to heterotrophs that utilize inorganic compounds or geological processes as their source of electrons?",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "Lithotrophs",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Biology",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Ecology", "Energy Sources"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 6,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "What is a perfect flower?",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "A perfect flower is one in which both male and female reproductive structures are present. / Both androecium and gynoecium are located on the same flower",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Biology",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Botany", "Flower Anatomy"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 7,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Why was VALCO, the first aluminum smelter company in Ghana, sited at Tema in the Greater Accra Region.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "Sited at Tema so as to receive imported alumina through the Tema harbour and also having electricity supply from Akosombo.",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Chemistry",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Industrial Chemistry", "Location Factors"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 8,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Why is the electrolysis of molten alumina preferred to electrolysis of an aqueous solution of $\\mathrm{Al}^{3+}$ ions in the commercial production of aluminium?",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "$\\mathrm{H}^{+}$ions in the aqueous solution will be discharged at the cathode in preference to the $\\mathrm{Al}^{3+}$ ions $\\mathrm{OR}$ the reduction potential of $\\mathrm{H}^{+}$ions is higher than that of $\\mathrm{Al}^{3+}$.",
    //     "calculations present": "No",
    //     "Subject": "Chemistry",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Electrochemistry", "Aluminum Production"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 9,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Calculate the $\\mathrm{pH}$ of 0.100 moldm $^{-3}$ solution of a sodium salt of an alkanoic acid whose $\\mathrm{pK}_{\\mathrm{a}}$ is 4.80 .",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "$\\mathrm{pK} \\mathrm{b}_{\\mathrm{b}}$ of the conjugate base $=14.0-4.80=9.20$\n$$\n\\begin{array}{rlrl}\n\\mathrm{pOH} & =1 / 2 \\mathrm{pK}_{\\mathrm{b}-} \\quad 1 / 2 \\log \\mathrm{C}_{\\mathrm{b}} & \\left(C_{b}=0.100 \\mathrm{moldm}^{-3}\\right) \\\\\n& =9.20 / 2+0.500=5.10 \\\\\n\\text { Hence } \\mathrm{pH} & =14.0-5.10=8.90 .\n\\end{array}\n$$",
    //     "direct_answer": "8.90",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Chemistry",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Acid-Base Chemistry", "pH Calculation"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 10,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "What is the work done by an ideal gas in a process in which its volume changes from $2.0 \\mathrm{~m}^{3}$ to $6.0 \\mathrm{~m}^{3}$ at a constant pressure of $200 \\mathrm{kPa}$ ?",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "$800 \\mathrm{~kJ}$",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Physics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Thermodynamics", "Work Done"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 11,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "Find the resistance of a resistor which dissipates $200 \\mathrm{~W}$ when the current through it is $5 \\mathrm{~A}$.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "$8 \\Omega$",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Physics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Electricity", "Resistance Calculation"]
    // },
    // {
    //     "S/N": 12,
    //     "Has Preamble": "No",
    //     "Preamble Text": null,
    //     "Question": "A $2 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object moving at $5 \\mathrm{~ms}^{-1}$ collides head-on with and becomes attached to a stationary $1 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object. Give the direction in which the objects move relative to the velocity of the incoming object.",
    //     "Question has figure": "No",
    //     "Question figure name": null,
    //     "Answer has figure": "No",
    //     "Answer figure name": null,
    //     "Answer": "They move in the same direction as the incoming object",
    //     "calculations present": "Yes",
    //     "Subject": "Physics",
    //     "Topic Tag": ["Mechanics", "Conservation of Momentum"]
    // }
]

export default contest_1_2